صفر بالمية، فش بطرية
0/100 there’s no battery
والاكترية بدون هوية
and the majority have no identity
ما في امان، الوضع تعبان
There’s no safety, the situation’s bad
اخر الزمان، تعبان تعبان
Lately, it’s bad
الواضح انو فش امل
Cleary there’s no hope
جماعة ماشية على الهبل
People are functioning on stupidity
وعند الاغلبية ما في اولوية
And the majority have no priorities
والاكترية شلة همل
and they’re all a bunch of bums
لا في مصاري ولا راحة بال
There’s neither money nor peace of mind
ماشي لحالي ضايع من زمان
I’ve been on this road alone, Lost forever
لا في مصاري ولا راحة بال
There’s neither money nor peace of mind
ماشي لحالي ضايع من زمان
I’ve been on this road alone, Lost forever
الواضح انو فش امل
Cleary there’s no hope
جماعة ماشية على الهبل
People are functioning on stupidity
وعند الاغلبية ما في اولوية
And the majority have no priorities
والاكترية شلة همل
and they’re all a bunch of bums
خلصت السهرة، طفت الموسيقى
The night is over, the music’s gone
وصلت الفتورة، شو الحل؟
The bill is here, what’s the solution?
خربت السيارة، وعم بتشتي حجارة
The car broke down, and it’s raining stones
واذا بيجي بكرا، شو ضل؟
And if tomorrow comes, what left?
الواضح انو فش امل
Cleary there’s no hope
جماعة ماشية على الهبل
People are functioning on stupidity
وعند الاغلبية ما في اولوية
And the majority have no priorities
والاكترية شلة همل
and they’re all a bunch of bums
وعند الاغلبية ما في مسؤولية
And the majority have no responsibilities
والبقية شلة همل
And the rest are A bunch of bums